<idea-plugin>
    <id>io.github.mingovvv.endpoint-lens</id>
    <name>Endpoint Lens</name>
    <vendor email="mingovvv@gmail.com">mingovvv</vendor>
    <description>
        Endpoint Lens helps you understand Spring HTTP mappings in large projects.
        It indexes controller endpoints, provides fast search/navigation, and warns about duplicate mappings before they cause runtime confusion.
    </description>
    <change-notes><![CDATA[
      <p><b>1.1.1</b></p>
      <ul>
        <li>Improved generic type resolution — dynamically unwraps unknown wrapper types (Callable, CompletableFuture, etc.) without a hardcoded list.</li>
        <li>Fixed generic record parsing (e.g. PageResponseDto&lt;T&gt;) that previously produced empty JSON.</li>
        <li>Enum fields now render as "ENUM" instead of empty objects.</li>
        <li>Date/time types (OffsetDateTime, ZonedDateTime, etc.) now display their type name instead of empty objects.</li>
        <li>@Schema example values are used in JSON preview when available.</li>
      </ul>
      <p><b>1.1.0</b></p>
      <ul>
        <li>Added Response JSON Structure preview panel — instantly see the response shape of any selected endpoint.</li>
        <li>Improved search UX: dedicated search field with magnifier icon and one-click clear button.</li>
        <li>Enhanced search highlight with high-visibility yellow markers for matched tokens.</li>
        <li>Redesigned filter layout — Method and Module filters on the first row, Controller on the second row, all column-aligned.</li>
        <li>Popup now closes automatically when navigating to an endpoint via Enter or double-click.</li>
        <li>Location display in search results now shows only filename and line number for cleaner readability.</li>
        <li>Endpoint count status label added below filters showing how many results are visible.</li>
        <li>Updated tool window icon to match the plugin's visual identity.</li>
      </ul>
      <p><b>1.0.0</b></p>
      <ul>
        <li>Initial release of Endpoint Lens.</li>
        <li>Project-wide indexing of Spring HTTP endpoints.</li>
        <li>Searchable endpoint navigation via tool window and popup action.</li>
        <li>Duplicate endpoint inspection with IDE warnings.</li>
      </ul>
    ]]></change-notes>

    <depends>com.intellij.modules.platform</depends>

    <extensions defaultExtensionNs="com.intellij">
        <toolWindow id="Endpoint Lens"
                    anchor="right"
                    icon="/icons/endpointLensToolWindow.svg"
                    factoryClass="mingovvv.endpointlens.idea.ui.HttpPathsToolWindowFactory"/>
        <postStartupActivity implementation="mingovvv.endpointlens.idea.index.EndpointStartupActivity"/>
        <localInspection language="any"
                         shortName="HPS001DuplicateEndpoint"
                         id="HPS001_DUPLICATE_ENDPOINT"
                         displayName="Duplicate HTTP endpoint"
                         groupName="Endpoint Lens"
                         enabledByDefault="true"
                         level="WARNING"
                         implementationClass="mingovvv.endpointlens.idea.inspection.EndpointDuplicateInspection"/>
    </extensions>

    <actions>
        <action id="EndpointLens.OpenHttpPathsPopup"
                class="mingovvv.endpointlens.idea.ui.OpenHttpPathsPopupAction"
                icon="/icons/endpointLensToolWindow.svg"
                text="Open Endpoint Lens Popup"
                description="Open Endpoint Lens search popup">
            <add-to-group group-id="MainMenu" anchor="last"/>
            <add-to-group group-id="ToolsMenu" anchor="last"/>
            <keyboard-shortcut keymap="$default" first-keystroke="control alt H"/>
        </action>
    </actions>
</idea-plugin>
